Guide to the Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, Records SC0252
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- GPU/GLAS Records
  - Series I
    - "Once Around The Quad" listings, Stanford Daily (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - San Jose Mercury News (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Media relations (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - The Stanford Daily (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - SAE fraternity "gay liberation" pledge stunt (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - BAYMEC [Bay Area Municipal Elections Committee] (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bomb threat at "choosing children" (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Security clearances (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Moot Court protest, 1985 May (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - California State Legislature AB-1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - California State Legislature AB-168 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - S. F. gay bath-house closure (protest statement) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Tearoom activity (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Office telephone, Stanford (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Annoyance call complaints, Pacific Telephone, 1983- (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Segal sculpture (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Out (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Stanford administration correspondence - In (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Stanford organizations correspondence - In (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - G & L artistic/cultural entertainment correspondence - In (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Commercial correspondence - In (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Non-gay commercial correspondence - In (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Non-gay organizations correspondence - In (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Gay organizations correspondence - In (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Scientific surveys correspondence - In (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - In (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Misc. records (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gertrude Stein Week, 1985 Apr (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - RPDS Education Project, 1986 Jan (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Peninsula Gay, Lesbian, & Bisexual Awareness program - misc. organizational papers, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Restricted files
      - Misc. correspondence - In with responses., 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence - In, Personal, 1978-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Phone Messages (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence-In-Personal, 1978-1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Personal Correspondence - In (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - SF Gay Bath House Closure - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Series II
    This series is comprised of the office records of the Gay Community of Concern (GCC). Files include extensive information on gay and lesbian organizations in Santa Clara and San Mateo Counties during the early to mid-1970s. Other materials found in this series include: organizational resources (health, churches, governmental); Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation records; and the correspondence of Dick Lewis (Director of GCC). In addition, the emergency information referral records of the GCC are also held in this series, as are the counseling and referral records of individual clients.
    Counseling records are restricted and will not be opened for use until 2060.
    - Agencies - General; no file established (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - California, State of. Department of Public Healh (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Canada College, Redwood City (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Capp St. Foundation (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Catholic Social Service, San Mateo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Catholic Social Service of Santa Clara County, San Jose (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Catholic Social Services - Helen Hansen [San Francisco] (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Center for the Advanced Study of the Behavioral Sciences (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Center for Creativity and Growth, Palo Alto (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Center for Research on Women - C.R.O.W. at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Charles Drew Health Center, East Palo Alto (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Children's Health Council (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Children's Protective Services (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Churches - San Mateo [Redwood City Unitarian Fellowship] (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Churches - Santa Clara (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Columbae House (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Common College, Woodside (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Community Health Abuse Council (CHAC) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Assoc. Santa Clara County (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Conference on Religion, Race and Social Concern of Santa Clara County (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Congress for Continuance of the American Revolution (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Contact Telephone Ministeries, San Jose (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Counseling Center for Women (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Crystal Springs Rehabilitation (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Damiel Switchboard, Daly City (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Dann Services, Inc. Dr. Kuldaw (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - De Anza College (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Economic and Social Opportunities Inc.; Women's Alliance (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - El Camino Hospital, 2500 Grant Road (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - El Camino House (formerly Mental Health Recovery, Inc.) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - E. O. C. San Mateo County (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - E. S. O. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Ethnic Minority Association of California (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Family Counseling Center (Family Crisis Center) Redwood City (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Family Service Agency of San Mateo County (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Family Service Association of the Mid-Peninsula (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Family Service Association of Santa Clara County (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Foothill Jr. College (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Foster City Police Dept. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Gestalt Institute for Growth (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Good Samaritan Hospital (Los Gatos) (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - "Grantsmanship" - see "Funding" (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Haight-Ashsbury Free Medical Clinic (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Health Systems Agency of S. C. C. (see Comp. Health Planning) (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - High schools (general) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Home health services (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Hospitals (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Human Investment Project - S. M. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Information Project of Peninsula Library System (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Involvement Corps (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Jewish Community Center (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - KKUP FM (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - KPFA - Fruit Punch (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Kaiser Permanente - Redwood City (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - La Casa de las Madres (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Langley Porter Neuro (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Media lists (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Men's Center (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health Association of San Mateo County (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Mental Health Association of Santa Clara County (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mental Health Assoc. of S. C. Co. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health Recovery, Belmont (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mental Health Recovery, Inc., Belmont. Now called Caminar Pedrigal House (9/26/1975) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mental Research Institute Srvcs. bill (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitan Transportation Commission (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ming Quong Children's Home (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miramonte Mental Health Services (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Misc. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Mission Mental Health (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Mountain View, City of (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Mountain View High School District (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Mountain View Methadone (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mountain View Police Department (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - National Institute of Mental Health. N.I.M.H. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Palo Alto Clinic (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Palo Alto - Police Departments & Los Altos (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Palo Alto Recreation Dept. (fees) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Palo Alto - Schools (curriculum) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Palo Alto schools - personnel policy (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Palo Alto Times (newspaper) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Palo Alto YMCA (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Parental Stress Hotline - Palo Alto (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Pathway (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Peninsula School (Menlo Park) (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - People's College of Law, L. A. Gay Lawyers & Law Students; Third World; Lesbians. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Population Institute (Washington, D.C.) (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Probe Center Community Involvement Corps, R.C. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Project Outreach, Redwood City (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Prometheus (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Psychological Integration Institute (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Psychosynthesis Institute (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Raleigh Hills Hospital: alcohol treatment facility (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Ravenswood H. S. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Redwood City (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Redwood House (Caminar) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on Minorities & Women, Redwood City (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Redwood City Halfway House (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Jack's Halfway House, Redwood City (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Redwood High School (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Redwood City Task Force on Social Counseling (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Regional Young Adult Project (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rehabilitation Mental Health Services (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Religious groups (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Research (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Research, general (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Research - Lists search (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Retreat (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Rogers, Martin. Ph.D. at California State Univ. Psych. Dept. [Sacramento] (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Rosenberg Foundation (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Salvation Army (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco Foundation (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - San Jose (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - San Jose City Human Relations Commission (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - San Jose State (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - San Mateo County (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - San Mateo County Adult Probation (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - San Mateo County Board of Education, Redwood City (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - San Mateo County Board of Supervisors (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - San Mateo Comprehensive Health Planning (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - San Mateo County. Department of Public Health & Welfare, Social Service Department (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - San Mateo County Human Relations Commission (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - San Mateo County Juvenile Probation (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - San Mateo County Non Discrimination Ordinance (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - San Mateo County. Dept. of Public Health & Welfare. Mental Health Services Division (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - San Mateo Legal Aid (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - San Mateo Co. Suicide Prevention Center (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Santa Clara county - Juvenile Probation Department (Box 4)
    - Santa Clara Co. Mental Health Advisory Board & Bureau (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Santa Clara County Mental Heath Bureau, San Jose (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Santa Clara Manpower Board (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Santa Clara Co. - Misc. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Santa Clara County. Office of Superintendent of Education, Special Services (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Santa Clara County Probation: Child Sexual Abuse Treatment Program (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Santa Clara County. Dept. of Public Health. Mental Health Services - Central county (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Santa Clara County. Human Relations Commission (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Santa Clara County. Department of Public Health. Mental Health Services - North county (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Santa Clara County. Department of Social Services, San Jose (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Santa Clara County Health Dept. Alcohol Outpatient Services centers (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Santa Clara County. Adult Probation, San Jose (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Santa Clara County. Social Planning Council (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Santa Clara County Area Agency on Aging (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Santa Clara County Public Defender (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Santa Clara County United Fund (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Santa Clara University (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Santa Clara University. Institute on Sexism (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Santa Clara County: Council of Churches (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Santa Clara Co. Democratic Party (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Self help clinics - Literature, etc. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Senate Bill #39 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Sequoia High School District (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Sequoia Hospital (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Service League of San Mateo (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Sexual law reform (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Social Planning Council of Santa Clara County (see United Fund), Santa Clara (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Stambaugh Counseling Center (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Stanford Medical Center (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Gender identification - Stanford Univ. Medical Center (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Memorial Church, Stanford University (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Stanford - Police Department (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Stanford Univ. Dept. of Psychiatry (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Stanford University - services to students (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Stanford ASSU (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Stanford University Student Affairs (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Senate Public Works Committee (The Advocate) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Saga Foods (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Stanbaugh House (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Stanford - Cowell Student Health Center (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Stanford Univ. Career & Placement Center (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Stanford Daily (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Stanford Christian Fellowship (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Stanford - (Daily) (Dept. Sociology) Center for Interdisciplinary Research (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Stanford dormitories (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Stanford. Tresidder Student Union lecture series (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Stanford Women's Center (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - United Bay Area Crusade (UBAC) (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture. Food stamps (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - United States. Probation and parole (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Van Loben Sels Foundation (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - V. A. Hospital, Menlo Park (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Bureau - Voluntary Action Center, 460 Calif. Ave., Palo Alto 94306 326-9381 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Ward Atmospheric Scale (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Welfare Recipients League, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Women Against Rape, San Mateo (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Women in Apprenticeship Program (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Women's centers - Misc. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Western Institute for Group and Family Therapy (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Women's Coffee House Collective, P.A. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Women's Rehabilitation Association, San Mateo (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - YWCA (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Youth Advocates (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Zellerbach Family Fund (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Alanon for Gays (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Bay Area Gay Liberation (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Berkeley. Office of the Mayor (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Bibliography (gay publications) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Blackberri (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Briarpatch Cooperative Auto Shop (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Brown, Howard M.D. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Bridge (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Brothers Behind Bars (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Center for Homosexual Education, Evaluation, and Research (CHEER), S. F. State Univ. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Christopher Street Democratic Club (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Crux Lauren. Workshops (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Daughters of Bilitis (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Delphi (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Dignity (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Extended Living Room (see Our House for ideas) (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Fruit Punch (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Gay Academic Union (National) Hunter College (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Gay Academic Union of Northern Calif. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - GAU Conference in New York, 1974 Nov 29-30 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Gay American Indians, S.F. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Gay Coalition on the Media (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Gay Freedom Celebration (see GPU 6/74 Conference & Gay Pride), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Gay Health Workers (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Gay Community Services Center - L.A. (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Gay Involvement Way (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Gay Involvement Way - Peninsula (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Gay Liberation/Arizona Desert (GLAD) (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Gay Nurses Association (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - GPO Counseling Collective (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Gay People's Union - Canada College (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Gay organizations - Misc. (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Gay Prisoners Relief. Dick Price, National Coordinator (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Gay Referral Switchboard, S.F. (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Gay Students Coalition (S.F. City College) (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Gay student organizations (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Gay Teachers' Coalition (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Gay youth advocates (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Dr. Garrad [or Gerrad?] (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Golden Gate Gay Liberation House - Emmaus Foundation (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Gregorio, Arlen - State Senator (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Hastings [Law School]: Gay Law Students Association (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Integrity: Gay Episcopal Forum (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lesbian Feminist Alliance, San Jose (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Lesbians In Law (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian Mothers Union (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dick Lewis (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eli Leon (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Men's Liberation - Steve Hansen (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - M.C.C. [Metropolitan Community Church] San Jose. Chirho counseling line (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - M.C.C. Oakland (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - National Gay Task Force (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Office of the Emperor of San Francisco (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Office of the Emperor of San Jose (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Operation Concern, Pacific Medical Center (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Pacific Center (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Parents of Gay People: S.F. County (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Parents of Gays (Santa Clara Co. Mental Health) (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Peninsula Group of Concern (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Pride Foundation (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Prisoners concerns and needs (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Publications (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Religion and gay people (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Renaissance House - Gay Yellow Pages (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Sacramento Women's Center & Bookstore (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Salmacis (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco Men's Switchboard (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - S.F. organizations (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Santa Clara Co. Gay Community Resources Group (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Santa Cruz Lesbian & Gay Men's Union (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - The Sentinele - S.F. newspaper (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Stanford Law School (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Stein, T. J. Berkeley (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Training (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Transexual (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - United States Mission (prisoners' homophile group) (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Volunteers (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Women's concerns (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - West Valley College Gay Org. (ORGY) (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - GPU Women's Collective - contact sheets and misc. documents, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Project: Gay Community of Concern contract riginals (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Gay Community of Concern: letters of support (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Gay Community of Concern - Professional Advisory Committee (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - GCC Advisory Council: Bylaws, contracts, etc. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Gay Community of Concern - correspondence (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - [GCC] Activities log (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Contracts: State Dept. of Health, Mental Health Center (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - GCC - Misc. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Gay Community of Concern - Misc., 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - GCC - Office appointment calendars (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - GCC - Misc. statments and office blanks (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Tasks (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Evaluation forms for project (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - GCC staff meetings, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Gay Community of Concern - Statistics (file by date) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Statistics (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Statistics (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Gay Community of Concern - Publicity (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gay Community of Concern - Questions and answers (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gay Community of Concern - statistical forms (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Time Cards G.S.R.A. [Gay Support Resources Agency] (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - G.S.R.A. records - service by phone (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Friends of Gay Community of Concern (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Dick - correspondence (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Patrick Gandy (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Frederick L. Oberg (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Whitman-Radclyffe [Foundation] minutes of board meetings (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Whitman-Radclyffe correspondence (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Contact forms - Whitman-Radclyffe copy (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising ideas (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Funding: grants, applications, methods (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Contact forms pending: most recent week, ending Friday (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Extra copies of directory stuff (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Employers (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - E.S.O. [Economic and Social Opportunities Inc.] grant proposal (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Health concerns - people interested in: workshops, conference, seminars (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - HEW - Office of Education Region VIII Training & Resource Center (see: Awareness House, Inc.) (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - High school youth - correspondence (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Housing discrimination (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Political info. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings on homosexuality (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - [GCC] Professional Advisory Council membership sign up lists (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Printing, copying - rates, places (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Publications / publishing houses (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - GCC - monthly time sheets (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Gay Community of Concern - phone logs (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - GCC telephone call sheets (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - GCC phone log (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - One: the homosexual magazine. v.IV no.4 (April-May 1956) Gift of the National Gay Archives, 9/81 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Misc. correspondence and flyers (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - SWOPSI 169 Gay Studies Course -- proposal, correspondence, etc., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Gay Support Resource Agency (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University News Service - press releases - for Archives (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Palo Alto School Board anti-discrimination policy, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Dick Lewis - personal letters re Gay Community of concern (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Dick Lewis - personal GCC files - correspondence (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Lewis - personal - GCC: Fair Oaks Community Center (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Lewis - personal - Focus proposal (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Dick Lewis - personal - "Gay Youth Advocates" proposal (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Lewis - personal - GCC: copies of letters to Michael Silverstein (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Whitman-Radclyffe Foundation contribution form (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Holograph notebooks (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Holograph notebooks (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Gay Community of Concern. Misc. materials (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings, gay-related, 1975 fall-1976 winter (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Articles on gender identity (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Local resources: employment agencies, drug abuse facilities [printouts from a database], 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Everywoman Women's Center, Palo Alto (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Legal resources (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Gay resources (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Counseling resources [printouts from a database], 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Alcohol resources [printouts from a database], 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)